Finding Aid to the Save the Redwoods League photograph collection. 1885-2014
The Bancroft Library
- Series 1: Vertical Files., 1897-2014; cartons 1-8; A box 1; AX box 1, folders 1-20; B box 1, folders 1-15, 17-18; C box 1; D folder 1; F folder 1; H folder 1; NEG boxes 1-5; NEG(gl) boxes 1, 3, 8, 9; NNEG boxes 1-6
  - Metasequoia glyptostroboides (Dawn Redwood)., 1948-1989 (Carton 5)
    4 matching copy negatives removed to NEG box 1.
  - Miscellaneous people., circa 1920? -1928, undated (Carton 5)
    Includes people cooking over a camp ground fireplace; Dr. J.C. Merriam standing by rocks off the Columbia Highway?; Colonel Graves and party examining range on Upper Porcupine Creek in the Gallatin Basin; Judge Childs with Sheriff Breen; an unidentified photographer; Sequoyah; Ralph W. Bull standing near bridge.
    2 negatives (1 matching and 1 related studio portrait of unidentified man) removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Miscellaneous people, oversize., 1939, undated; 2 photographs (Ax box 1, Folder 15)
    Studio portrait of Allan C. Balch, by Gabriel Moulin, 1939; studio portrait of an unidentified man, by Blank and Stoller, New York.
  - Miscellaneous people, oversize., 1939, undated; 2 photographs (B box 1, Folder 9)
    Studio portraits by Blackstone Studios, New York and Kay Hart Studios, New York. Following names accompany the portraits: F.A. Delano; Dibble. It is unclear if names are the sitters.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (identified locations)., 1913-1969 (Carton 5)
    Includes Lane's Redwood Flat; Russian River; Mission San Juan Bautista; giant black oak at East Windsor; Sacramento River and Mount Shasta; landscapes near Kennett, Calif.; Grant's Pass; Morongo Pass; Joshua tree (negative only); entrance to Hidden Spring; Old Columbia, Tuolumne County; Oregon redwoods; Black Forest, Germany; hemlock trees in Washington; mule deer at Gunnison Utah; Roosevelt Elk at the Bronx Zoo.
    2 negatives (1 matching and 1 related of Highway at Grimes Canyon) removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (identified locations), oversize., circa 1920 (A box 1, Folder 6)
    Photographs of Bolling Grove and South Fork of Eel River mounted on a board.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (unidentified locations, black and white photographs., 1918-1965; 2 folders (Carton 5)
    Includes photographs by Russell Angel, Moulin Studios and Martin Litton.
    5 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 2.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (unidentified locations), color photographs., 1997-1999 (Carton 5)
    Many are snapshots.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (unidentified locations), oversize., 1999 (A box 1, Folder 6)
    Color panoramic view snapshots related to smaller snapshots shelved as -- PIC.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (unidentified locations), oversize., 1 photograph (Ax box 1, Folder 16)
    Stream in forest.
  - Miscellaneous photographs (unidentified locations), oversize., 1997; 3 photographs (C box 1, Folder 9)
    Aerial view of California coast. Specific location unknown. All copies of same print.
    Photo from WAC Corporation, number WAC-97CA 12-1513.
  - Miscellaneous printed material., circa 1941-1971 (Carton 5)
    Includes greeting card related to redwood trees and fund raising brochures.
  - Miscellaneous printed material, oversize., circa 1955-2014; 2 items (B box 1, Folder 1)
    Menu from The Whitcomb Hotel with redwood trees on the cover. Poster commemorating 150 years of California State Parks.
  - Mondale with redwood tree., September 26, 1984 (Carton 5)
    Former Vice President Walter Mondale presented with a California redwood tree by Sierra Club President Mitchell Perault at a presidential campaign rally. Folder contains 1 item.
  - Monterey County., 1919-1969, undated; 2 folders (Carton 5)
    Includes Pacific Grove, Monterey, Saddle Rock Falls, Notleys Landing, Big Sur River, Pfeiffer's Beach, Pfeiffer's Resort, Littler Sur River and South Fork of Little Sur River, Palo Colorado Canyon, Castro Canyon, Port Canyon, Molera Ranch, Grime's Beach, Castro Ranch, Anderson Canyon area. Also includes brochures and maps.
    Includes photographs by Lawton, Josselyn, Bendore, Newton B. Drury and George Openhym.
    See also: Julia Pfeiffer Burns State Park, and Little Sur River and Bixby Creek, Big Sur folders.
    2 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 3. 2 related negatives of Palo Colorado removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Monterey County -- Josselyn photographs., circa 1920s-1930s (Carton 5)
    Photographs taken by Lewis Josselyn of Carmel. Includes Palo Colorado Canyon, Torres Canyon, U.S. Forest Service ranger headquarters at Big Sur, Pio Blanco from near the sea, Little Sur River and Slates's Hot Springs.
  - Monterey County -- Oliver Collection., 1897-1929 (Carton 5)
    Copy prints and copy negatives, numbered 12329-12373. Originals date 1897-1929. Includes Point Lobos, Cypress Point, women picnicking at Cypress Grove.
    18 copy negatives (14 matching and 4 related) removed to NEG box 3. 17 copy negatives (10 matching and 7 related) removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Monterey County -- Pfeiffer Ranch, Big Sur River., 1 photograph (G folder 1)
    Panoramic landscape of meadow. Verso: Monterey Chamber of Commerce, A.W. Files, Pres. 5725.
  - Monterey County -- Slevin photographs., 1913-1929 (Carton 5)
    Photographs taken by L.S. Slevin of Carmel. Includes Idlewild near Big Sur, Sur Post Office, Malpaso Canyon, Palo Colorado Canyon and Garapatos Canyon.
  - Montgomery Woods State Reserve (Mendocino County)., 1919-1967 (Carton 5)
    Includes photographs by Mrs. Edward Ayer
    3 matching copy negatives removed to NEG box 1. 7 negatives (5 matching and 2 related) removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Montgomery Woods State Reserve -- 83-500., 1983 (Carton 5)
  - Morro Bay., circa 1935; 2 photographs (H folder 1)
    Panoramic landscapes. Photographs by Frank Aston photographer, San Luis Obispo, Calif. (file number 6225), and Aerograph Co., L.A., Calif., 1763 W. Vernon (number 708).
  - Moulin photographs., 1926, circa 1955; 12 photographs (B box 1, Folder 10)
    Photographs by Gabriel Moulin Studios. Includes 11 panoramas of the mouth of Bull Creek, Dyerville Flat, South Fork of Eel River near Dyerville and near Fish Creek and Redwood Highway. One labeled on back: Forest Glimpses along the Redwood Highway.
  - Muir Woods National Monument (Marin County)., 1928- 1973 (Carton 5)
    Includes National Conference on State Parks barbeque in 1928, United Nations delegates at a commemorative ceremony for Franklin D. Roosevelt, Mount Tamalpais, John B. Dewitt with Marlin Perkins and Marvin Hershey.
    Includes photographs by Moulin, H.S. Lawton, Lawton and McClure, F. Ransome, Madison Devlin (contact sheets).
    3 matching copy negatives removed to NEG boxes 1 and 4.
    - United Nations delegates at a commemorative ceremony for Franklin D. Roosevelt, Muir Woods., May 19, 1945; BANC PIC 2006.030--PIC; 1 photograph (Carton 5)
      Photograph by James A. Lawrence, numbered: 8280.
      This material was selectively digitized from a larger resource or collection. From folder: Muir Woods National Monument.
      Marin County (Calif.)
  - Muir Woods National Monument, oversize., 1922?- May 1945; 5 photographs (C box 1, Folders 6-8)
    Panorama of 3 photographs on 1 mount, by Tibbits; 2 photographs mounted on board of delegates to First United Nations Conference, San Francisco, in the redwoods.
  - Muir Woods National Monument -- 03-009., September 23, 2003 (Carton 5)
    Color snapshots of a group of people on a redwood tour.
  - National Park Service Region 4 picnic., July 25,1947 (Carton 5)
    Include Newton B. Drury, William E. Colby, Herbert Mauer, Harlan Jones, Aubrey Neasham and O.A. Tomlinson.
  - National Park Advisory Board tour of the redwoods., 1968-06-28 (Carton 5)
    Includes Frank E. Masland, Ralph W. Chaney, Newton B. Drury and Frank Setzler.
  - Navarro River Redwoods State Park (Mendocino County)., 1985 (Carton 5)
    Includes Dimmick Memorial Grove State Park.
    Includes photographs by Scott, Howard King and Don Briggs.
    75 matching and related 35mm negatives (3 rolls) removed to NEG box 2.
  - Navarro River Redwoods State Park -- 85-500., 1985 (Carton 5)
  - Oakland parks., circa 1920? (Carton 5)
    Includes Lake Merritt, Redwood Regional Park, and Mayor John L. Davie of Oakland.
    Includes photographs by Lawton and M.L. Cohen.
  - Olmsted, Frederick Law, Jr., circa 1953 (Carton 5)
    Includes Olmsted hold his dedication plaque.
  - Oregon Caves National Monument and Preserve., circa 1920s-circa1935 (Carton 5)
    Includes people at campfire and views inside the caves.
  - Patrick's Point State Park (Humboldt County)., 1930-1964 (Carton 5)
    5 copy negatives (3 matching 2 related) removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Patrick's Point State Park (Humboldt County)., 1930-1933 (A box 1, Folder 7)
    2 panoramic views made from several pieced together photographs.
    5 matching negatives removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Petrified Forest (Sonoma County). (Carton 5)
    Includes brochures.
  - Pfeiffer Big Sur State Park (Monterey County). (Carton 5)
    Snapshots that include the main campground.
    28 matching 35mm negatives removed to NEG box 2.
  - Photo releases., September 2005-August 2006 (Carton 5)
    Prints of digital photos with signed photo and identification release forms for various schools field trips, and related correspondence.
  - Piedmont Garden Club tour of Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park., May 24, 1970 (Carton 5)
    Includes Newton B. Drury, Thomas A. Greig, Ralph W. Chaney, John B. Dewitt, Lyle Keith, Mr. and Mrs. Harmon Bell.
  - Pillsbury Photograph Company photographs., 1920s?; 3 photographs (A box 1, Folder 8)
    Jumbo and General Freemont Trees in Big Basin; General Sherman Tree in Sequoia; Grizzly Giant Tree in Yosemite National Park. Identified as 1920s, but probably earlier.
  - Pillsbury Photograph Company photographs., 1906-1907; 6 photographs (B box 1, Folder 11)
    Includes Cloistered Aisle in Big Basin, Redwoods State Park and Sequoia Park.
  - Pinto Lake redwood planting, Portola Expedition., October 2, 1948
    No prints available.
    7 negatives removed to NEG box 1.
  - Point Lobos State Park (Monterey County)., circa 1920s-1954; 2 folders (Carton 5)
    Includes San Jose (Monastery) Creek Beach, areal views and a program for the dedication of the park as a national natural landmark.
    Includes photographs by Gabriel Moulin, Newton B. Drury, Laidlaw Williams and Martin.
    6 matching negatives removed to NEG box 1. 40 negatives (17 matching and 23 related) removed to NNEG box 3. 14 negatives (4 matching and 10 related) removed to NNEG box 6.
  - Point Lobos State Park, oversize., circa 1928; 2 photographs (B box 1, Folder 17)
    Aerial views. Includes a photograph by Fairchild Aerial Surveys.
  - Point Lobos State Park -- Berhman photographs., August 2, 1891 (Carton 5)
    Two Martin Behrman photographs of people posing at Point Lobos.
  - Point Lobos State Park -- Knight photographs., 1937 (Carton 5)
    Photographs by Emerson Knight.
    Save -the-Redwood League numbers 12283-12284,12381-12382.
  - Point Lobos State Park -- Riley photographs., circa 1898-1922, undated (Carton 5)
  - Portola Redwoods State Park (San Mateo)., 1969-1987, undated
    Includes Chesebrough Property, Grove P-152, Grove P-150, Hooper Grove
    Includes photographs by David Swanlund, and Howard King.
  - Portola Redwoods State Park, oversize., 1987 (A box 1, Folder 9)
  - Portola Redwoods State Park-- 82-500., 1982 (Carton 5)
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park (Humboldt County), black and white photographs., 1913-1993; 2 folders (Carton 6)
    Includes mining camp at Gold Bluffs, near Fern Canyon in 1913; Carothers property; people at the dedication of the California Children's Grove, Amony Creek; Big Tree.
    Includes photographs by Russell Angel, Moulin Studios, David Swanlund and Philip Hyde.
    7 negatives (4 matching and 3 related) removed to NEG box 1. 20 related 35mm negatives removed to NEG box 2. 2 related negatives removed to NNEG box 3.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park (Humboldt County), color photographs. (Carton 6)
    Includes clear cut area.
    Includes photographs by Howard King, Larry Ulrich, Evan Johnson and Mary Angle-Franzini.
    1 photo CD removed to NEG box 1.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park, oversize., 1966?; 1 photograph (Ax box 1, Folder 17)
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Aerial views., 1961-1971 (Carton 6)
    Bulk are of Fern Canyon and Gold Bluffs.
    Includes photographs by David Swanlund, Robert W. Ford, Howard King, Martin Litton, Moulin Studios and Philip Hyde.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Aerial views, oversize., 1 photograph (C box 1, Folder 9)
    Aerial view of a clear cut forest. Photograph by Gabriel Moulin Studios
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Arcata Redwood Company lands., 1950-1973 (Carton 6)
    Land owned by, or formerly owned by, Arcata Redwood Company, which is adjacent to Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park, or became part of the Park.
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, John E. Gutteridge, Howard King, Glen Jones and Robert Ford.
    20 negatives (9 matching and 11 related) removed to NEG box 1.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Duncan McDuffie and Jean Howard McDuffie Memorial Grove., 1950s-1960s (Carton 5)
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios and John E. Gutteridge.
    6 negatives (5 matching and 1 related) removed to NEG box 1.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Elk., 1932-1993 (Carton 6)
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, Emerson Knight, Newton B. Drury, Tom Myers, Thomas A. Greig and David Swanlund.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Fern Canyon., 1958-1970; 2 folders (Carton 6)
    Includes Thomas A. Greig, Ralph W. Chaney, Newton B. Drury and John B. Dewitt standing at the mouth of Fern Canyon
    Includes photographs by David Swanlund, Moulin Studios, Philip Hyde, Ken Legg, Doug Dill, Martin Litton and Howard King.
    7 matching negatives removed to NEG box 1.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Fern Canyon, oversize., 2 photographs (B box 1, Folder 3)
    Color photograph by David Swanlund. 2 copies of same image.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Freeway construction., 1964-1965 (Carton 6)
    Construction of Highway 101 section to bypass the park.
    Includes photographs by Martin Litton, David Swanlund and Newton B. Drury.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Freeway construction, oversize., 1964; 2 photographs (C box 1, Folder 10)
    Construction of Highway 101 section to bypass the park. 2 copies of same image. Photographs by Martin Litton.
    Used for exhibit or display.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Gold Bluffs Beach, black and white photographs., 1963-1977; 2 folders (Carton 6)
    Includes photographs by Newton B. Drury, Philip Hyde, David Swanlund and Tom Myers.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Gold Bluffs Beach, color photographs., 1963-1997 (Carton 6)
    Includes photographs by L.C. Merriam, Newton B. Drury, John Haas, David Swanlund, Howard King and Evan Johnson.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Gold Bluffs Beach, oversize., 1964; 2 photographs (Ax box 1, Folder 17)
    Gold Bluffs Beach, photograph by Doug Yule. Elk on Gold Bluffs Beach, photograph by Martin Litton.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Gold Bluffs Beach, oversize., 1969; 3 photographs (D folder 3)
    Photographs by David H. Swanlund (numbers 43 and 44). Two are copies of different sizes.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Gold Bluffs Beach, oversize., 1963? (F folder 1)
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Gold Bluffs Beach -- Money presentation in Governor's office., January 18, 1966 (Carton 6)
    Save-the-Redwoods League presenting deed and facsimiles of checks for Gold Bluffs, Fern Canyon purchase to Governor Edmund G. Brown. Includes Francis P. Farquhar, Governor Brown, Richard M. Leonard, Fred L. Jones and Newton B. Drury.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Groves., 1953-1993, undated (Carton 6)
    Various identified groves or tracts. Includes National Council of State Garden Club Grove, Elizabeth B.E. Roberts Memorial Redwood Grove, Charles G. Woodbury Grove, Vira Georgeson Ferguson and William C. Ferguson Grove, Grove of Happy Memories, Robert and Leona Train Rienow Redwood Grove, Charles P. and Elizabeth Harmon Howard Grove, John B. Dewitt speaking at the dedication of the Newton B. Drury and Aubrey Drury Memorial Grove, Hunnewell-Donald Grove, and Declaration of Independence Grove.
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, John Gutteridge, David Swanlund, Philip Hyde, Martin Litton and Evan Johnson.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Groves -- King photographs., 1965-1972 (Carton 6)
    Photographs by Howard King of various identified groves or tracts.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Groves, oversize., 1959; 2 photographs (B box 1, Folder 3)
    Bakewell Grove and Hunnewell- Donald Grove marker. Photographs by John E. Gutteridge (numbers G-11, H-3).
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Highway photographs by Swanlund., 1963-1972; 3 folders (Carton 6)
    Includes 2 complete sets of photographs by David Swanlund, duplicates and a map to memorial groves with key to photos.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- James Irvine Grove and Trail., 1920s-1967, undated (Carton 6)
    Includes Godwood Creek area and Big Tree.
    Includes photographs by Tibbits, Russell Angel, Emerson Knight, and John Gutteridge.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- James Irvine Grove and Trail -- Moulin photographs., 1953, undated (Carton 6)
    Includes Godwood Creek area.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Moore Tract, Pacific Coast Lumber., 1968, 1976 (Carton 6)
    Includes snapshots related to memorandum from Lawrence C. Merriam to Mr. Drury.
    9 negatives (1 matching and 8 related) removed to NEG box 3.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Newton B. Drury Scenic Parkway dedication., October 3, 1993 (Carton 6)
    Includes John B. Dewitt.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Rotary Club members at Rotary Memorial Grove., 2002 (Carton 6)
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- Ulrich photographs., 1975-1983 (Carton 6)
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 39-500., 1939 (Carton 6)
    Spens Black Grove. Folder contains 1 item.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 44-500., 1944 (Carton 6)
    Includes Big Tree in James Irvine Grove (also identified as Elk Grove).
    Includes photographs by Moulin Studios, Tibbitts and Martin.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 45-500., 1945 (Carton 6)
    Bruce Lyon Memorial Grove. Photographs by Moulin Studios.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 46-500., 1946 (Carton 6)
    Fabens Memorial Grove. Folder contains 1 item. Photographs by Moulin Studios.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 47-500., 1947 (Carton 6)
    Soroptimist Grove and Gladys Quarre Knapp Redwood Grove. Photographs by Moulin Studios.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 48-500., 1948 (Carton 6)
    Includes Johnson Grove and Grove 102.
    Photographs by Moulin Studios and John Gutteridge.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 50-500., 1950 (Carton 6)
    Ada Fenimore Bock Grove.
    Photographs by John Gutteridge and Moulin Studios.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 51-500., 1951 (Carton 6)
    C.A. Schenck Grove, Frederick Law Olmsted Grove, Ben, Mary and Sprague Johnson Grove, William May Garland Memorial Grove, Charles Lockhart McKelvy Grove, Grove 21 D and Grove 61.
    Photographs by Moulin Studios.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 52-500., 1952 (Carton 6)
    E. Bruce Merriman Memorial Grove, Charles Lockhart McKelvy Grove and Rotary Memorial Redwood Grove.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 53-500., 1953 (Carton 6)
    Grove Z 1 through Z 3 and Z 5. Photographs by Moulin Studios.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 53-501., 1953 (Carton 6)
    John C. Brickell Memorial Grove and Grove X 53. Photographs by John Gutteridge.
    6 negatives (2 matching and 4 related) removed to NEG box 5.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 56-500., 1956 (Carton 6)
    8 negatives (2 matching and 6 related) removed to NEG box 5.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 58-500., 1958 (Carton 6)
    Welch Grove, Chickering Grove and Chickering Grove bench with plaque.
    Photographs by Moulin Studios and David Swanlund.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 60-500., 1960 (Carton 6)
    Robert Gordon McKay Memorial Grove. Folder contains 1 item. Photograph by Moulin Studios.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 63-500., 1963 (Carton 6)
    Includes Adams Memorial Grove, Declaration of Independence Grove, Angeline Boardman Kirk Memorial Grove, Newton and Aubrey Drury Grove, Elizabeth B.E. Roberts Memorial Grove and Lincoln Ellsworth Grove.
    Photographs by Moulin Studios, John Gutteridge and David Swanlund.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 64-500., 1964 (Carton 6)
    Helen Stelzner Grove. Folder contains 1 item. Photograph by David Swanlund.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 65-500., 1965 (Carton 6)
    Florence, Francis and Jane Loomis Grove, Marguerite and Ernest Bloch Memorial Grove, Edward D. and Nella K. Armstrong Memorial Grove, Eugene Waddell Britt Grove, James W. Buel Memorial Grove, Hooker Grove, Dewey Donnell Grove, Glenn McClelland Donnell Memorial Grove, Leonard and Marguerite Liermann Grove and William May Garland, 11 Grove (seashore).
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 65-501., 1965 (Carton 6)
    Robert Gordon McKay Memorial Grove, R.D. Merrill Memorial Grove, National, Herbert L. Nichols Grove, Frank and Ida Pauson Grove, Albert B. and Margaret Kirk Ruddock Redwood Grove, Council of State Garden Clubs Grove, Beatrice S. and Daniel G. Volkmann Grove, Mabel H. Weeden Grove, John and Elizabeth Claflin Grove, Grove X-A 1 (seashore), Grove X-A 2, Grove X 53A and Gold Bluffs Beach.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 65-502., 1965 (Carton 6)
    Declaration of Independence Grove, John and Elizabeth Claflin Grove, Lincoln Ellsworth Memorial Grove, Elliott Memorial Grove, Ruddock Grove, Grove of Happy Memories.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 66-500., 1966 (Carton 6)
    John Glascock Baldwin Grove. Photographs by David Swanlund.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 67-500., 1967 (Carton 6)
    Mabel Lund Greig Grove, and Thomas K. and Susan McCarthy Grove
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 68-500., 1968 (Carton 6)
    Includes Marguerite and Ernest Bloch Memorial Grove, plaques and benches in Volkmann, Greig and Ferguson Groves, Lucy H. Hume Memorial Grove, and Ella Goad Hooker and Charles Osgood Hooker Grove.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 69-500., 1969 (Carton 6)
    Gertrude Strong Achilles Memorial Grove (including plaque and bench), Ethel Hulbert Bloodgood Grove, Children's Grove, J.B. Sprague Johnson and Olive Alida Perry Johnson Grove, Robert L. Lipman Memorial Grove, McEuen Family Grove, Charles and Florence Mel Redwood Grove, Walter Schroeder Memorial Grove, and Grove X 146A.
    Photographs by David Swanlund, John Gutteridge and Howard King.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 70-500., 1970 (Carton 6)
    James W. Buel Memorial Grove, Louise Ireland Granger Grove, Herbert L. Nichols Grove, Chauncey P. Pond, Jr. Memorial Grove, Karl and Sophie Rothschild Memorial Grove and Arthur A. Schmidt Memorial Grove.
  - Prairie Creek Redwoods State Park -- 71-500., 1971 (Carton 6)